To host your Streamlit app on Streamlit Sharing, follow these steps:

1. Push your Streamlit app to a public GitHub repository. Make sure your repository contains all necessary files to run your app, including equirements.txt for any necessary Python packages.

2. Visit [Streamlit Sharing](https://share.streamlit.io/) and click on the 'Sign in with GitHub' button. If you haven't used Streamlit Sharing before, you'll need to request access and wait for an invitation.

3. Once you're signed in, click on the 'New app' button.

4. In the 'GitHub repository' field, enter the name of your GitHub repository. It should be in the format username/repository.

5. In the 'Branch' field, select the branch that contains your Streamlit app.

6. In the 'File path' field, enter the path to your Streamlit app file within your repository.

7. Click on 'Deploy' to deploy your app.

Your Streamlit app should now be live on Streamlit Sharing. You can share the URL with anyone you want to show your app to.
